<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Plan-O</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="subject_string">Subject:</string>
    <string name="type_string">Type:</string>

    <string name="add_task">Add Task</string>
    <string name="add_exam">Add Exam</string>
    <string name="add_reminder">Add Reminder</string>

    <string name="priority_string">Priority: </string>
    <string name="date_string">Date:</string>
    <string name="no_date_set_string">00/00/00</string>
    <string name="change_date_string">Change Date</string>
    <string name="enter_details_string">Enter Details</string>
    <string name="cancel_string">Cancel</string>
    <string name="submit_string">Submit</string>
    <string name="enter_title_string">Enter Title</string>

    <string name="spinner_prompt">Select</string>
    <string-array name="subject_list">
        <item>CSIT111</item>
        <item>CSIT113</item>
        <item>CSIT114</item>
        <item>CSIT128</item>
        <item>CSIT115</item>
        <item>CSIT212</item>
        <item>CSIT314</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="task_type_list">
        <item>Homework</item>
        <item>Project</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="exam_type_list">
        <item>Quiz</item>
        <item>Test</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="empty_fragment_string">There\'s nothing here! Tap on the plus to add new to-do items.</string>

    <string name="termsAndCondition">
Last updated: 10-10-2019 \n
        Please read these Terms and Conditions carefully before using
        the <b>http://www.Plan-O.com</b> website and Plan-O mobile
application (the "Service") operated by Plan-O.
Your access to and use of the Service is conditioned on your acceptance of and compliance with
these Terms. These Terms apply to all visitors, users and others who access or use the Service. \n\n

<b></b>\n\n

<b></b>\n\n
If you wish to purchase any product or service made available through the Service ("Purchase"),
you may be asked to supply certain information relevant to your Purchase including, without
limitation, your …
The Purchases section is for businesses that sell online (physical or digital). For the full
disclosure section, create your own Terms and Conditions. \n\n

<b></b>\n\n
Some parts of the Service are billed on a subscription basis ("Subscription(s)"). You will be billed in
advance on a recurring …
The Subscriptions section is for SaaS businesses. For the full disclosure section, create your
own Terms and Conditions. \n\n

<b></b>\n\n
Our Service allows you to post, link, store, share and otherwise make available certain information,
text, graphics, videos, or other material ("Content"). You are responsible for the …
The Content section is for businesses that allow users to create, edit, share, make content on
their websites or apps. For the full disclosure section, create your own Terms and Conditions. \n\n

<b></b>\n\n
Our Service may contain links to third-party web sites or services that are not owned or controlled
by Plan-O.
My Company (change this) has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content,
privacy policies, or practices of any third party web sites or services. You further acknowledge and
agree that My Company (change this) shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any
damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any
such content, goods or services available on or through any such web sites or services. \n\n

<b></b>\n\n
We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms at any time. If a
revision is material we will try to provide at least 30 (change this) days\' notice prior to any new terms
taking effect. What constitutes a material change will be determined at our sole discretion. \n\n
        <b></b>\n\n
If you have any questions about these Terms, please contact us.
    </string>

    <string name="privacyText">
        Last updated: 10-10-2019 \n
Plan-O operates http://www.Plan-O.com. This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of
Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.
We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you
agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. \n\n
<b></b>\n\n
While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information
that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not
limited to your name ("Personal Information"). \n\n
<b></b>\n\n
Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site
("Log Data").
This Log Data may include information such as your computer\'s Internet Protocol ("IP") address,
browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit,
the time spent on those pages and other statistics.
In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and
analyze this …
The Log Data section is for businesses that use analytics or tracking services in websites or
apps, like Google Analytics. For the full disclosure section, create your own Privacy Policy. \n\n
<b></b>\n\n
We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional
materials and other information that …
The Communications section is for businesses that may contact users via email (email
newsletters) or other methods. For the full disclosure section, create your own Privacy Policy. \n\n
<b></b>\n\n
Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier.
Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer\'s hard drive.
Like many sites, we use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all
cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may
not be able to use some portions of our Site. \n\n
<b></b>\n\n
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of
transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to
use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its
absolute security. \n\n
<b></b>\n\n
This Privacy Policy is effective as of (add date) and will remain in effect except with respect to any
changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this
page.
We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this
Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the
Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your
consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.
If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email
address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website. \n\n
<b></b>\n\n
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
    </string>
</resources>
